From telescopes to the large head on collider
망원경부터 대형 강입자 충돌기까지
each new scientific tool will invent revise the questions
새로운 과학적 도구들은 우리가 과학자로서
that we as a scientists
그리고 호기심 많은 사람으로서
and curious minds can reasonably ask
합리적으로 물어볼 수 있는 질문들을 새롭게 만들어왔어요
high performance computing or hbc
고성능 컴퓨팅, 즉 HPC는
joined that elite list in the sixties today
60년대에 그 엘리트 목록에 합류했어요. 오늘날
quantum computers are knocking at the same door.
quantum 컴퓨터들이 같은 문을 두드리고 있습니다.
Welcome my name is is conducive to coffee
안녕하세요, 저는 IBM Quantum의
and i'm software engineer here at ibm quantum
소프트웨어 엔지니어예요
in this course we aim to teach students
이 과정에서 저희는 학생들과
and professionals ally how quantum computing will soon
전문가들에게 quantum computing이 곧
work together with hbc infrastructures
HPC 인프라와 함께
to deliver computat
어떻게 연산을 제공하게 될지 가르치려고 해요
you will learn how quantum
quantum과
and classical computers communicate and exchange data
고전 컴퓨터가 어떻게 통신하고 데이터를 교환하는지,
how to write programs that exploit both types of hardware
두 가지 유형의 하드웨어를 활용하는 프로그램 작성법,
and how this integration open sub applications we can solve today
그리고 이 통합이 오늘날 해결할 수 있는 애플리케이션들을 어떻게 여는지 배울 거예요
you'll build practical experience with real quantum hardware
실제 quantum 하드웨어와
and classical high performance computing clusters
고전적인 고성능 컴퓨팅 클러스터를 통해
running quantum jobs alongside traditional hbc workloads
전통적인 HPC 워크로드와 함께 quantum 작업을 실행하는
and keep use interpret results with confidence
실용적인 경험을 쌓고 결과를 자신 있게 해석하며
and identify places where quantum acceleration
quantum 가속이 계산에 실질적으로
could genuinely help calculations
도움이 될 수 있는 곳과
and where it doesn't above all you will understand
그렇지 않은 곳을 파악하게 될 거예요. 무엇보다도 컴퓨터의 미래가
where the future of computers headed
어디로 향하고 있는지,
and the old map that will take us there we think
그리고 거기에 도달하기 위한 로드맵을 이해하게 될 거예요. 저희는
this course is both important
이 과정이 중요하고
and timely and we believe
시의적절하다고 생각하며,
combining this technologies will be essential
이 기술들을 결합하는 게 계산적 우위를
to achieving computational advantage
달성하는 데 필수적일 거라고 믿어요
this could have wide ranging impacts across industries
이건 화학 같은 다양한 산업에 광범위한 영향을 미칠 수 있어요
like chemistry possibly enabling
더 빠른 신약 설계와 소재 연구를
faster drug design and materials research
가능하게 하거나,
in finance
금융에서는
for smarter risk models
더 스마트한 위험 모델과
and fraud detection in artificial intelligence in machine learning
사기 탐지, 인공지능과 머신러닝에서는
for model optimisation in this course
모델 최적화에 활용될 수 있어요. 이 과정에서
will dive deep into computer resources
컴퓨터 자원에 대해 깊이 파고들고
programming models and quantum all greater
프로그래밍 모델과 quantum 알고리즘을 다룰 거예요
so welcome and get crazy
환영합니다, 함께 즐겁게 해봐요
a lot to discuss
이야기할 게 정말 많아요